# Anci Sun

## UX Designer

#### Contact

0

Sacramento, CA

ancisun04@gmail.com

(916) 870-9695

(H)

ancisun.com

in

linkedin.com/in/ancisun

Bē

behance.net/ancisun

## UX Skills

Interviewing

Surveys

Card sorting

User research

Usability testing

Competitive analysis

User personas

Wireframing

Prototyping

Information architecture

Storyboarding

Visual design

Sitemaps

HTML/CSS/Javascript

# Tools

Adobe XD Figma

Sketch Balsamiq

Illustrator Invision
Photoshop Axure

Atom Webflow

A Sacramento-based User Experience Designer coming from a background in recruiting. The theme throughout my caerer is being a problem solver, whether it's analyzing feedback to improve hiring processes or connecting with stakeholders to collaborate on solutions. I'm committed to contributing my skills and knowledge to solve complex problems in an effort to promote a safer, user-friendlier world.

## Experience

#### UX Designer & Researcher I Motherhood Design

November 2019 - present, remote

Motherhood is a community of designers and product makers who create products and services to keep mothers happy and healthy.

- Collaborate with researchers, designers, and content strategists to facilitate user research to inform MVP and set a plan for adjustments in the next 3-month sprint
- Conduct surveys and gather feedback for company website redesign
- Collaborate with designers on UI guidelines for website redesign

#### **UX Designer I We Connect The Dots**

November 2019 - present, remote

Empowering every student with the opportunity to succeed through experiential learning programs.

- Collaborate with designers, developers, and CEO to set a plan for website redesign
- Conduct usability testing to understand how users interact with the current website
- Create low-fidelity wireframes through Figma to ensure a functional website with proper flow and navigation

#### Independent UX Designer I Self-Employed

October 2019 - present, Sacramento

Help independent businesses optimize their products through user research and redesigns without compromising the user experience.

- Collaborate with lead developer on note-taking app redesign that's currently available for Android users (Fluid Notes)
- Synthesize user feedback to identify areas of improvement and execute implementation of requested features by creating an updated sitemap and lo-fi wireframes via Adobe XD

#### Education

UX Design Certificate | CareerFoundry

April 2019 - November 2019

BA, Political Science/English | UC Berkeley

August 2013 - May 2017